Hello everyone, welcome to another edition of This Just In, back by popular demand, I have with me Marco from ItalianPod.
Ciao, ciao, I'm Marco too.
No, Marco, no, you could be Marco one.
No, no, it's okay, you know, like your people like you here at EnglishPod.
I came to your house, it's not nice to, you know...
You are Marco one.
No, no, you could be Marco one.
No, no, you are Marco the first.
How about you are Marco one and I'm Marco two?
No, I seriously...
No, seriously...
No, you could be Marco...
Look.
Come on, you...
Look, don't, you are Marco one.
You could be Marco...
No.
I'm telling you.
Hey, guys, guys, what are you doing again?
Come on.
What is this about now?
Leo from SpanishPod again to come and ruin our fun.
Leo from SpanishPod, hi.
You guys are always fighting, what is this about now?
No, it's just, he doesn't want to be called Marco one.
So what if you are like Marco three and Marco four?
That'd be stupid.
That makes no sense.
You want to be Marco one and two at the same time?
It's like...
No, no, no.
So what are we here for, Marco?
Maybe we should beat him up a bit.
Yeah, let's beat him up a bit.
No, no, no!
Okay, okay, enough, enough.
Enough fighting, all right.
So what are we here for?
Okay, today we're going to be talking about our lessons for next week.
By the way, you scream like a girl when you are a bit...
No, that was Leo.
Ah, yeah, was it?
I was telling you how you get serious.
What is it?
How you get...
Okay, okay, go on, get serious.
Next week we're going to have a lesson related to the presidential elections.
Wow.
You're late.
Yeah, a little bit.
No, it's going to be about the president talking at his presidential inauguration.
When is that going to be, huh?
I think officially it's January 20th or something like that.
At noon, if I'm not mistaken.
Exactly.
Their time.
So they were practicing.
Yeah.
Yeah, they were rehearsing.
So we're going to have a lesson about that.
I want to miss it.
We're going to cut that out.
I said I want to miss it.
I thought you said I want to miss it.
No, no, no, no.
I said I want to miss it.
You see, guys, where you have to study with English poets and you have faults.
Yeah, you can improve your pronunciation.
Or you're listening.
We also have a lesson called He's Not a Good Fit.
Basically, a manager is complaining about one of his employees because he says he doesn't
have good work ethics.
Oh, so he's not a good person, kind of?
Like he's chatting on his computer instead of talking to customers and stuff like that.
Ah, well, yes.
That's, yeah.
Of course.
We don't do that.
Not allowed.
Yeah, that should be punished.
Yeah, yeah.
Because we don't do that.
No.
Zero tolerance in this office pod.
Office pod, no.
Zero tolerance.
He doesn't support this kind of behavior.
Exactly.
Out.
And we have the third episode of I'm Sorry I Love You.
Oh, I can't wait for it.
Wow.
Yeah, yeah.
Is it romantic?
It is romantic, but I think they get into a fight.
So drama.
Drama.
Do we get to see anything that is rated R and is a bit, eh?
No, not yet.
Spicy.
Last time, I think I listened to the swooshing on some bad sheets.
And I think it was a bit spicy, wasn't it?
Yeah, it was kind of hot.
All right, I don't know what you guys are thinking.
It was just a kiss.
Anywho, what about the promotion market?
Exactly.
As you all know, we have a promotion right now where you can pay for 12 months and you
get 15 months.
No way.
Way.
We're telling you.
15 months for the price of 12.
This is $69, right?
Exactly.
$69 for an entire 15 months.
So the promotion is only until January the 31st.
So you're only going to have access to the elementary lessons for free.
The rest of it, you're going to have to pay for it.
So get a 12-month promotion.
Exactly.
Don't miss out.
I'm going to do it.
Yeah, don't miss out.
So you can improve your pronunciation.
Or I can just go to Marco's desk and ask him some advice.
But I will do it.
I will do it too.
Exactly.
We're going to be coming out with a lot more content.
We're going to have more lessons.
We're going to come out with extra shows also.
So we're going to have a lot of other things to offer.
Yeah, also the biography of Marco is coming out.
Yeah.
Is it true?
My memoirs.
Yeah.
Maybe.
It's called My Life on the Edge.
I heard it's about 200 pages biography.
Is it?
Just the first volume.
It's a 10-volume book.
Spicy.
Yeah.
That's spicy.
Exactly.
Now let's talk about the user of the week.
Is it me?
I think it was me, man.
No.
You guys don't even go to the website.
Hey, I commented.
Me too.
I commented.
Once.
No.
I started a whole conversation about who pays for who.
At dinner?
Yeah.
It was controversial.
I liked it.
Well, anyways, the user of the week is Princess Aisha.
Princess Aisha.
Where is she from?
Exotic.
She's from Pakistan.
Spicy.
That's spicy.
Princess Aisha.
Aisha.
Aisha!
Aikote moa!
Why is she the user of the month and not Leo that started a very interesting conversation?
Yeah, why is she so special?
Because she's commented on a lot of our lessons.
And she's been asking some really good questions, so ...
And she's beautiful.
Yes, she probably is.
So if I comment her a lot, can I be the next user?
No, because you're ugly.
Exactly.
You can.
All right.
But maybe we can give you like a peloush, a peloush.
What do you call it?
It's teddy bears.
a teddy bear. But if it's not a bear? A teddy cat? A stuffed animal? Pelouche. Is that French
or Italian? I think we might have borrowed the word for a few years. Give it back. Alright
so congratulations Princess Aisha. Congratulations. Keep up the good work. Alright. Brava. So
that's it right? That's it. Okay we're out of time for today so be sure to go to our
website. Leave all your questions and comments and we'll be there to answer and I'm sure Marco
and Lea will also be commenting more on our website. Yeah. Marco one. Man Marco two. They
might not give us permission to come back next week on the News and Future show. So yes.
So it's been a hell of a ride and we hope you liked it. Alright guys we'll see you later.
See ya folks. Bye. Child. EnglishPod.com